I surrender like just when I think I'm
surrendered yeah I surrendered I'm here
I'm willing to do my mission I'm willing
to do my path like another layer every
single time
and that's life it's growing and
learning but the fact that this thing
unfolds in front of me in front of us
together as we as we move forward is
both like ridiculous I get how
ridiculous it is but it's happening and
so I've gotten to the far enough part
along my path to be able to showcase it
to have enough faith in it where I'm
like okay if this is crazy then hey
please it'll be entertaining Lisa look
I'll go down having fun
you know we're all the collapse but it's
like it's happening it's already
happening it happens like all by myself
up until the point I found the people
the game be happened now it's happening
and all the conversations that find
their way to me because that's what I
can do but there's this way I'm able to
talk when the camera is not on this is
powerful indeed and then when the camera
turns on it's just not the same and it's
even less the same when I'm live on
camera partly that is because I am
trying to explain something I'm trying
to explain it in a way that people
understand it and get it knowing I can't
actually do that okay somebody could but
I cannot and because it's not supposed
to be it's supposed to be
exactly what it is because it's supposed
to unfold in front of you
all you being the collective you that
gets to watch this me being the me that
gets to experience it and look a fool at
the beginning and then it's gonna happen
before my eyes and before your eyes
we're going to create a world that works
for everyone
my life is intertwined with it but I
also just got well I was singing my
daughter to sleep that what I've been
missing because I keep explaining like I
swear I'm here to save the world and I
have a side to you it's gonna save us
all but I can't explain it and how
ridiculous that is right it's gonna
unfold in front of you so that's fine
and I don't even need to explain that to
you because it's not a it's not a
commercial it's not a trailer that's not
enticing people in because it's not
explaining to them what's in it for them
what I can make clear when I'm talking
to myself
off-camera is what is in it for you
which is that I'm not unique I'm not the
only one who gets to live my genius and
gets to be the savior of humanity what
it's what we get to do together it's
what like anyone who wants to be a part
of it gets to live into their genius and
follow their roadmap and get to have all
of the gifts that are waiting for you
along the way you don't have to
sacrifice everything wait till some
afterlife and get some reward that's
promise to you or sacrifice hurt your
fellow human beings and get some
financial reward that's waiting for you
you can live a life that's meaningful
where you have everything you need you
have the people you care about and who
care about you you get to be your
authentic self you get to figure out why
you are here and get the tools to be
able to do that in a way that works for
you how does that work because every
single piece of that is somebody else's
genius it's their path it's the thing
they're here to do they want to do it
pays
to do it it is an internal motivation to
do that and so what's in it for me is
that I get all of your genius I get to
give by genius and I get to experience a
world where humanity is unleashed where
our ingenuity our ingenuity our
creativity what we are capable of gets
to get better and better and better
because we can tap a little more into it
and a little more into it and it proves
it along the way the individual path
proves it to use you keep going and the
group path proves it
we keep creating stuff that is enjoyable
to be part of that is fun and easy to
use
and when it's not we own it we improve
it and create better we start me and we
get better and better as we go and it
already is it man
okay like the thing that it is like yes
we haven't created the product yet in no
way is the tech cooperative actually up
the grunting like I mean no totally is
but it's not we don't have a tech thing
right we're not like hey sign on here
you sign up for the MailChimp newsletter
they don't even know the URL of but the
right people are coming on board to you
let's do that piece we're creating so
this video was supposed to be about I
think I will do two because it needs to
have to I don't know what this one's
gonna be called but what I plan to do is
show up here recording my thoughts
saying what I want to say not what I
should say or what I think I should say
to explain it you thought I know it was
not doing that anyway but there was it's
like trying to it's that next layer of
like oh okay
I don't need likes I don't need
subscribers what I needed is to speak
the truth my treat like explain the
journey showcase the journey because
we're gonna get there
and it's happening like before this was
the way to get there getting people on
YouTube was what it was because I didn't
have game B I didn't have a community I
didn't have these
verse Asians now it is happening it is
unfolding and we are showcasing it live
and so the I'm going to end this video
here I just wanted to share the pilot of
that series when I want to I'm gonna
record a video and put it up and I'm
gonna say what I want to say and I hope
I am able to learn how to more reliably
tap into speaking for my heart and
speaking with passion in a way that
people understand but if I try to do
that it's not gonna happen it has to be
speak from my heart and whatever comes
forth comes forth and so that's what
this video is is explaining that and
whatever I just spent last seven minutes
talking about thanks